So hello friend, in this video we will talk
about FP loan. Yes
friends, as I tell you,
friends, I have got a loan from FP, so
what is that loan, friends, how much is the
amount and how much is the charge,
I will tell you all the details in this video, just stay tuned to the
end of this video. So friends, first of all you
can see here that I have got a
loan here, which is mine, first of all
I will show you
how much amount is being deducted from my loan, you
can see here my daily amount is being
deducted proper, so you can see here
friends, I have to make a
loan payment of Rs 95000 here, now friends, let
us talk about how much loan I have got for the loan of Rs 95000,
or friends,
here I will show you in detail what
amount is being deducted from me and
what percentage is being charged, so
friends, first of all you can see here
that I will tell you all the details in this video
one by one, you just have to watch this video
till the end, so first of all
friends, here I  But let me show you
my percentage loan amount here, you
can see here, my
loan of 95000 here will be deducted from my account
and let me tell you this friends, this
merchant gets deducted automatically from your bank account
because friends, this
amount is automatically done by you through your PhonePe business itself,
if you
take a loan from here then you also get the option of loan payment, even
if you do not make the payment,
as soon as you
take the amount from that merchant, this amount will be deducted from your account and will
go into the PhonePe amount, so
friends, now let us talk about
how much loan I got, friends, here
I have got a loan of 75000 i.e. 75000,
which I can see here,
I have to pay something here
every day, which is ₹1 something here,
so you can see friends,
I have made a lot of loan payments here,
which is my automatic, every day
deducted here.  It is deducted from my bank account
which is from my PhonePe business account.
Here as soon as I take money in this amount here, then
my
amount here is automatically deducted and paid to the loan of FP.
So here
friends, it clearly means to you that if you
take a loan from here through FP Business App, then
you are given a loan here at a very low interest rate,
which is
for business. Yes friends, whoever has FP
Business App, they can see that loan here.
If you are not getting it, friends,
first of all you have to go and update FP
from PST. As soon as you
update it from PST, friends, then you will
get the loan here itself. Yes friends, the
loan here itself is 75000, 80000 and even
many people are getting a loan of Rs. 1 to 5 lakh here.
Friends, you
can see here that my loan has been
approved. If friends, your loan has
not been approved yet, then you
First of all,
I am showing you live here, so
friends, you can see me here, I have to
pay a loan of Rs. 75,000 here, that is, Rs.
95,000, which if I
talk about my interest rate here, then friends, here I am charging an
interest rate of about 12 to 14 percent, or
you can calculate it yourself and see that
I have to pay something extra here, Rs. 2,000,000,
which
you can see here, friends,
if you see the payment option here,
friends, you can also pay here,
whatever
business you have linked in Fpay, whatever
mobile number, you can also pay from that bank from here,
if
you want, you can see here, friends,
I can also see the option of pay here,
if I want, then
friends, I can already pay here,
like
whatever amount I have to pay for the coming day.  So here I will
click on pay, then my
amount will be paid automatically, so
friends, I will not pay here right now,
so friends, I have shown this here just to show you,
friends, you have to take the
payment only here, that
payment will be automatically deducted from the loan, so I
hope friends, I have told you this